hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft today
there's lots of little things going on
so there's no real big focus but there's
lots of things happening so I'm already
I'm gonna be meeting up with thee what
nope what Oh No and this is why you
always have to check your Electra oh my
goodness oh look at that mess I was
gonna say the first thing we're gonna do
is go to a meeting but it looks like the
first thing we're gonna do is don't
repair our light sure excuse me I'm
looking for my trident where is it oh I
didn't want to lose another trident I've
just realized how do I get up to the big
bad farm with help flying I'm basically
stuck down here this is where the did
you die box comes in very very useful
everyone should be buying one of these
and now I have to put up with this for
another 10 minutes well I'm just gonna
afk in here for a few minutes and then
we're gonna go back to the base where
this cow and mumbo are hopefully waiting
for me
hello guys this I think is the first
official architect meeting that involves
all three members yeah you have got a
VIP awesome I feel like I'm the child at
the end of the table of the diner you
know they have to bring up the special
chair anyway
let's get down to business guys cuz
we've got my own project if we're
getting down to business moustache for
your moustache for when you mean real
business as we all know Sahara is well
underway the project is making so much
progress and
got big plans we've sorted out with the
design and stuff but we need to let our
competitor which is Concorde know yeah
what's coming weed so give them a fair
warning I feel but I'm not entirely sure
what to do but I've got I got an idea
I'm gonna see if you guys are on the
same vibe okay so I'm curious what is
Sahara what is the in real life in real
life
okay geography what's the point in a
second mustache
if you don't know things when you yeah
yeah okay Escalus dressed like a very
typical geography teacher right now so I
thought I'd pass it over to my architect
suit teacher what are you talking about
okay it's a desert exactly he said I'm
proposing we dump a desert on Concord we
cover or the whole of young fall in san
big business opportunity for line and
it's gonna be like looking collect all
this and it'll be it's a great idea I
like it it's yeah brilliant all right
let's scare Concord then should we head
on over yes sounds good to me
take take that mustache off okay
okay have you ever been to Concord I've
not I've only ever flown over it's a bit
intimidating I once walked in and had a
piece of cake and it tasted greedy and
it wasn't at all all right should we try
and get it because we're basically just
gonna cover all of this inside I feel
like it's only right that we use the
front door so it says if you yeah if you
could dye the Sheep blue you are deemed
worthy of entering Concord I don't know
exactly what this means but I'm totally
going for it
what how did he yeah how did he do that
no I think worthy no it didn't go blue
it went yeah I'm fine
that is the pipe don't understand there
check that we're not worthy the joke is
that we know what I mean
i mumble you're a technical player since
I'm the geography teacher you can you
can explain what's going on here I'm
getting a bit tired
I think I might just
this is actually an easter egg in
Minecraft that came in 1.12 I believe
that no one noticed that they will read
I sheep they will case we're not worthy
no one is worthy yeah okay whatever
that's the coolest thing ever that I've
completely blown my mind alright let's
get ourselves set up I've got all the
shoka boxes we could possibly need
alright I guess let's get started
he'll be happy dude he would look at
this and be like hello Sam for days who
has a lot of sand and forgot to press f1
again this guy I did actually realize
and turned it off but it just keeps
happening anyway as you can see we
slowly covered the entire base line of
Concorde in sand and I thought this was
a pretty fun way to show Khan Corp that
their big competitor is on its way and
that we mean business we're not even in
business yet and we're already doing
stuff like this which means we could end
up with a very fun rivalry with Khan
Corp depending on how things go but I'm
really looking forward to the Sahara
project in general especially as you can
see the three of us we work quite well
together and in this case we wrote Khan
Corp a little warning message after
about an hour and a half I'd say of all
of us working non-stop this place is
looking pretty sandy and as you can see
we have warned Khan Corp where
suhara is coming and it's coming for you
Khan Corp there's no denying it let's
take a little fly around shall we cuz
this is looking really cool we've
actually covered all of the main part in
sand we didn't go overboard by you know
doing all this would have been kind of
pointless but all of there's even like
the fountain everything got done which I
don't know this I think this area looks
kind of cool actually I think we decided
after we'd finished we probably improved
Khan Corp warning Khan corpus I'd and
there's actually lots of things that I
need to do today so pranks out of the
way we've done that let's go back over
and work on some other projects now the
major thing that I've been working on is
of course the Sherlock Korean 2 to 1 G
Baker Street and I've actually made a
little bit of progress I've added a
lamppost and a rather temporary looking
bridge but on the inside I have actually
cleared out all the space now this isn't
going to be used which is why it looks
like a mess and you'll understand in a
minute why upstairs is where the real
magic is going to happen so you can see
this is much more room like now I've got
a pretty good idea of what I want this
to look like but there's two options
available to me and I'm gonna see what
each one looks like and then make a
decision the first one is like wall
panels that you get in these old-style
buildings this is very common but it's a
very very outdated
in today's building I think that that
will look very cool but it might be too
much wood the other option is that we
put quartz pillar down and then have
something like this in a more old
fashioned color that looks a bit like
wallpaper I think I'm gonna go with this
one just because there's already a
wooden floor and I think the contrast
would be quite nice but I don't think
I'm gonna go for the blue terracotta
I think that's actually quite nice
looking unfortunately there are no
windows I could do some like fake
windows that might look really cool
because I do actually need some light in
here it's
very very dark at the moment but I do
think what I could do is have a trim
around the top of it and then fill this
in with another color I've had quite an
expensive idea on how to do the ceiling
in here if I use daylight sensors
because it's got this like nice grid
pattern that you might expect from like
a wooden ceiling of some kind it I think
this will fit quite nicely actually
look how expensive these are to make
this is how much ever of God I don't
even think this is gonna be enough okay
so I've got the room set up now I think
that this actually works really well now
obviously there's only an empty room to
look at so it does look a little bit
different however I think I might have
the sort of Georgian style house
interior down very tall it's got a grid
pattern on the top it's got all of the
details around and the kind of wallpaper
and then even like the inside has wood
paneling now here look I don't really
fully understand how I've done this but
it looks like a sideways staircase this
is actually only four staircases but
because there's some on the other side
it's kind of like weirded out a little
bit I don't quite understand how this
has happened but it looks quite cool so
I'm gonna leave it as it is now all I've
got to do is make myself a nice big desk
and maybe some bookshelves and stuff
like that and I think we will be on to a
pretty cool-looking
office for Sherlock green and I actually
had a message from Wren of all people
saying that he needed my help and I said
that I was in the middle of doing this
and I will meet him a bit later on in my
base I need to crea heat like this that
you know the kind of bookshelves that
you have like a ladder and you can move
along but I really don't know what I'm
doing so I'm kind of just experimenting
also thanks to doc who supplied this to
me
but now we get to do one of my all-time
favorite minecraft decoration tricks
because he's given me a dragon egg well
I kind of bought
of him we can make one of my favorite
little tricks to do in the game it's
probably the weirdest use of the Dragon
egg or pointless use but with this you
can create a little lamp on a table I
absolutely love it I might end up
putting that on my desk but I think it
it sits quite nicely in the background
this room is really coming along I know
that it's full of brown at the moment
because of all the word and the ceiling
but I'm hoping I can fix that now I
really want to fill this up with lots of
things like a proper Sherlock Holmes
office would be so I've collected a
bunch of really weird stuff to put in
and hopefully this will add a bit of
colour that it desperately needs I'm
also gonna add some of the things that
are mysterious and we need to
investigate like the salmon man and
maybe just yeah random scar I mean it's
not really a mystery but I thought it'd
be cute I thought I could put like a bit
of coral here which should turn gray
give it a second
there we go grey and then a jukebox so
it's kind of like my like an
investigation type thing like a specimen
of some kind of course Sherlock Holmes
might have a bunch of different plants
or or herbs or something for his
experiments I'm gonna put those in there
that adds a little bit of green I've
bought two music discs that I think will
work quite well
yeah perfect now you guys know me and I
like to go a little bit overboard
sometimes most of the time and this is
going to be absolutely no exception but
I'm thinking we need like an
investigation room as well I'm gonna
need some carpets and all sorts but I
think this room is really really coming
together quite quickly
okay I've spent about an hour building
this room and this is what I've come up
with it's a very clean very nice office
with all of the little things that I
would associate Sherlock Green to have
there's lots of detail put in lots of
books a nice chair and desk good for
talking it to any customers that may
come along however there is a little bit
of a secret to this room I maybe went a
little bit overboard again but I've got
an investigation room in here this is my
board of connections I'm going to
investigate some of the biggest and most
mysterious cases on the server who is
the jingler who is the salmon and who is
poultry man we may never learn the
answers to these questions but in this
room which is significantly Messier
because I've tried to add lots of junk
everywhere we will get to the bottom of
it so this is my private secret private
room that should in theory be where I
can work things out but for now let's
keep it in the office all I've got left
to work out is how to get in and out
right now I've been just leaving through
the window but this is how you're going
to get in now you may have noticed that
down here I had a room that I'm not
using and that's because I have a very
very special way that I want to bring
clients up to my office so let's get
started on it it's going to involve a
little bit of red
stone the first thing that I definitely
am going to need is a doorbell and this
is going to be excellent so I already
need to thank family craft dad for
putting this together for me
because I really rubbish at music and
he's given me the instructions to do the
doorbell that I've asked for so thank
you family craft dad let's hope that
this works okay so I've got it set up
but I haven't actually put in the right
things for it so they're all the same at
the moment but this is what it sounds
like when it's all the same it's not
great and if you can work out what that
is without any of the actual things then
I will be really really impressed okay I
think it's done oh my goodness thank you
so much family crafts dad he's probably
gonna tell me it's I've done it wrong
but he does give me the most simple and
easy to understand instructions which I
really appreciate
listen to this everyone this is a very
famous English doorbell and that's
because it's not a doorbell
it's actually
[Music]
yeah it's the big it's like the Big Bend
sound oh it's absolutely gorgeous I love
this thank you so much family craft dad
now that isn't just where I'm going with
this now I need to actually make it so
that they can get in and it's going to
take a little bit of digging and red
stoning but I'm very used to that by now
okay
it is 100% finished maybe not the window
but hear me out I've completed an
entrance it's honestly not the best
entrance in fact I would say I really
need the help of someone who knows some
proper redstone but hear me out I've got
a proper doorbell a proper entrance and
a completed office so this is what
happens when you hit the doorbell it's
perfect it's what you might actually
expect at Sherlock Holmes office and
then it Chuck's you down here in the
slowest water thing ever which I'm
hoping you know just walk up a bubble
elevator and then into the office now I
really do need something better than
that something that pushes you super
quickly so like maybe Pistons with some
slime blocks like get pushed up this and
then you're here in Sherlock Green's
office so they'll come up and I'll be
like hello ready to provide some
consultation on mysteries but it's
actually been a lot longer than 30
minutes so I better go and actually meet
Wren now but I think I can open my shop
officially ready for business or ready
for mysteries as long as I actually make
a way out there is no way out except for
this hole in the window oh dear
so now it's time to tidy up and head
back over to the base mr. green hello
sir oh hey Ron one sec
it is a total mess in my base and I
cannot find my bricks oh really is a
mess
yes hi welcome to the ice he said don't
get too close
boy I've had a horrible realization this
morning I was sniffing around my base so
to speak and I suddenly realized that I
stink
rather horribly I think it's I think
it's the haste to but it looks like
there's actual stink particles coming up
rise I've been wearing these clothes for
10 years
come on let's have a let's have a little
sniff yeah yeah that's ten that's ten
strong years of Ren Ren the dog dude it
really looks like you're physically
stinking with life spy I need help man
okay help all right so what do you want
me to do about it well I have noticed
that you have a rather varietal wardrobe
so to speak I think of all the hermit's
you've probably the one that might be
able to help me oh yeah I'm picking up
what you're putting down mm-hmm bear
with me one second I know exactly what
to do all right let's uh let's move rent
rent two steps back oh yeah sorry right
well okay let's get you a new outfit so
what are we thinking for you Ren um well
you know I think I'm looking pretty
snazzy so to speak it's been many years
I I'm I'm not exactly the most stylish
of people of gee you looking super
snazzy though I think this is why you
got in touch I'm ready for every
eventuality I've got about I'd say 10 to
20 skins that have never been used
before but I'm ready for that situation
where I need them okay okay how can I
help you what do you need what do you
what do you feel like you want well I
mean yes I think are you Anna Taylor
outfit right now have you gone into
Taylor mode I've been
for this moment for about a year and a
half oh I see
I mean that's rather rude are you
implying that you've never really liked
nice gang very much you know it could
have been anybody skin but yes I don't
like your skin
let's check I have a selection of
clothing that has been sitting in my
wardrobe for 10 years maybe I could try
on a couple of those and maybe you know
you could do some tweaks here and there
just don't don't stick me with the
needle okay all right why don't we go to
a better backdrop so that we can check
out some of your outfits shall we say
and then I'm gonna take it from there
so if you have if you see the hole in
the top there if we go up to the the top
you'll there's a nice little space I
think we could use all right you've got
a bit of privacy there rent so you head
on behind get changed and let's see what
you got we've also great our re here is
also going to be judging you by the way
okay um no peeking okay private person
nope not looking I'm not looking
alright Korean you ready to see the
first outfit muddied oh I was born ready
right okay okay I'm cool okay right what
do we think
what are we ready when you said you've
got some skins to show me yeah I don't
like that doesn't mean your actual skin
okay right right let's just put you
straight behind there and let's go to
the next outfit because that's a that's
a hard no that's a hard no okay all
right Korean I've dug deeper into my
wardrobe okay I know I think I'm gonna
tell you something you're gonna like
it's jazzy it's snazzy Oh what do we
think well I think you've gone from too
little to too much right you've gone
from yeah from you've gone from not
wanting to look at you - I can't stop
looking at you in a bad way in a bad
okay what is on the front of your face
what are these yeah what are these
things
um they're little bows in my hair all
right well why don't you take those
little
is back behind the vanity curtain okay
and let's try again
alright it's a hard no T that's a very
hard no now bear in mind green I haven't
bought new clothes and ten years either
so I've had to dig pretty deep into my
wardrobe for this one okay do I even
want to turn around right are you ready
are you ready ah voila oh oh that's a
that's a whole lot of animal that's
animal listen particularly proud of the
other wait all right look just look look
down for me a second okay mmm-hmm okay
okay what what are we thinking what are
we thinking I'm I'm thinking what we do
is this is this is not a criticism okay
okay
I'm thinking that we put the cow costume
in the pen with the other cows and you
let me take over from here okay yeah I
think that's probably the best course of
action
all right go and get your other your
normal skin on and we'll start from
there okay okay all right I never wear
that again ever ever right okay okay
hold still hold still hold still now
hold still okay all right so I'm liking
I'm liking your color scheme I'm liking
the crease game the red and the blue it
works well
I'm thinking there's a few things we can
get rid of okay and the main one is your
face it's it's got to go we're gonna
need full honestly ran I don't know yeah
you've shaved your beard in the shape of
a smiley face and I cry seen nothing but
a smiley face all right
yeah so you know what is that before and
now that I'm looking closely I look at
absolutely ridiculous so right I'm
thinking suspenders
[Music]
full facial replacement surgery yard
surgery right couple of weeks recovery
you'll be fine
give me two minutes and you'll be
beautiful if you hop behind the vanity
curtain okay I'm gonna I'm gonna send
you send you what I'm thinking and then
we will evaluate all right if you have
an incinerator for these clothes because
seriously matters if the pungent odor is
I need you to send those to the moon for
me because if we burn them we're gonna
contribute to global warming all right
this feels so weird
oh man it's it's it's feeling like I
haven't been in clean clothes for so
long I know with whatever it's just walk
out like they own your new face okay and
all right here we go here we go that I
don't know if the world's ready for this
I don't know if I'm ready for this but
hi oh yes yes hello uh-huh that is I
mean you're not smiling anymore you got
a nice nice beard you you look you look
20 years younger
yeah I like the sunglasses
well the sunglass is your touch yeah I
may have made some custom sunglasses got
a bit of a Rolex on my on my risk too
and yeah I'm feeling pretty good man I'm
not gonna lie I mean this is this is a
new me dude I don't know what to tell
you I mean look at this I'm looking good
yeah do you feel good I'm feeling like a
million but I mean I I can start placing
blocks again come on let's let's see
what's under the glasses what's under
the glasses okay listen I'm trying to
adjust to mind you look okay so I have
it may be a bit of a surprise but oh
you know what you you're beautiful Ren
ya pop those back on for me okay oh
there he is okay that's the friend dog
we know and love
well Taylor gee you have done an
immaculate job I'm feeling like a
million dollars man I gotta take a while
for the odor to leave your base maybe
you want to make some ventilation holes
around here muddied up do is apologize
for that project yeah but I will point
out that you have done a pretty shoddy
job on your Jay on your shaving because
you're missing a few you're missing a
little bit there right yeah you Mona
grow that back somehow but okay laughing
swish and I hope the other Hermits
enjoy this as much as I have and now I
think that's all we have time for Ren
has had a proper and full makeover we
actually did go over all of the details
of his skin together and I think it
looks really really cool of course he
might decide to change it a little bit
but I think it's a really nice
improvement as someone that changes
their skin quite often I I approve of
this I think it's a really nice change
it's a very difficult thing to do so
honestly it would be great if everyone
could show Ren some support because it's
very nerve-wracking doing something like
that it's kind of like getting a crazy
haircut but in minecraft when you don't
know how your friends are gonna react I
realized that part of the Sherlock house
here isn't quite complete but now I
found my brick and it is pretty much
good to go so I'm afraid that is all I
have time for today thank you very much
for watching everyone I hope you've
enjoyed this episode
Sherlock rien should be in business very
very soon we've been we've been busy
today thank you very much for watching
as always guys and good
[Music]
okay one more time for you guys that
have stayed until after the goodbye
[Music]